designbold.com 2017-04-18

# Privacy Policy

This policy covers how DesignBold ("DesignBold," "we," "us," or "our") treats personal information that it collects and receives on www.designbold.com. We are not in the business of selling information about you: we use information shared with us for the sole purpose of running and improving our services. This notice tells you what information we collect, steps we take to protect and secure it, how we use and share information, and finally, how you can contact us with question or concerns.

### 1\. INFORMATION WE GATHER

DesignBold collects personal information when you register with us, use DesignBold products or services or post content on a DesignBold web site or blog. This information is limited to your email address, and any information you post on your site. Your password is stored securely using a salted, variable work factor, one-way hash function.

DesignBold automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request. We also collect other use information as part of our analytics services, in order to improve the service. However, we do not link such information to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. DesignBold may collect billing information if you sign up for a paid service, which may include your name, address, telephone number, credit card details, and other information that is necessary in order to process the transaction. Under no circumstance do we store any of your sensitive billing details. DesignBold uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, support, contact, research, and anonymous reporting.

### 2\. INFORMATION WE MAY RECEIVE FROM THIRD PARTIES

We may receive information about you from third parties. For example, if you access our websites or Service through a third-party connection or log-in, for example, through Facebook Connect, by “following,” “liking,” adding the DesignBold application, linking your account to the DesignBold Service, etc., that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to DesignBold. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account (for example, your Facebook UID), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us, and any information you have made public in connection with that service. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the DesignBold Service. You may also unlink your third party account from the Service by adjusting your settings on the third party service. If you unlink your third party account, we will no longer receive information collected about you in connection with that service.

### 3\. ANALYTICS INFORMATION

We may directly collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user.

### 4\. COOKIES

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to use DesignBold services or products that require you to "sign in" and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. DesignBold uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

• Require you to re-enter your password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents. Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using the DesignBold Sites, Products and Services.  
• Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.  
• Conduct research to improve the content and services provided on the DesignBold Sites, Products and Services. 

### 5\. IP Address

DesignBold occasionally obtains IP addresses from users depending upon how you access our web sites. IP addresses, browser and session information may be used for various purposes, including to:

• Diagnose and prevent service or technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.  
• Estimate the total number of users visiting DesignBold's web sites from specific geographical regions.  
• Help determine which users have access privileges to certain content, services or resources that we offer. Monitor and prevent fraud and abuse. 

### 6\. BILLING INFORMATION

When you purchase items on DesignBold’s web sites, we require your billing information in order to process the transaction. We will retain the last 4 digits of your credit card number and credit card type, so that you may identify that card used in the future. We do not store any other billing information, as this information is discarded after your transaction has been processed. All transactions are processed over an industry standard SSL/TLS connection, with a minimum of 128-bit encryption.

### 7\. INFORMATION RELATING TO CHILDREN

Individuals under the age of 13 are prohibited from creating or using accounts through DesignBold.com.

### 8\. INFORMATION USE, SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

DesignBold does not share personal information we learn about you from your use of the DesignBold’s web sites, products and services with others except as described in this policy. We do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes. 

DesignBold may use or share your personal information where it is necessary to complete a transaction, to operate or improve the DesignBold products and services, or to do something that you have asked us to do. We use other third parties such as a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes.

When you register for DesignBold, we collect user-submitted account information such as username and email address to identify users and send notifications related to the use of the service. When you post content on a DesignBold’s web sites or blog, you have the ability to post content which may include personally identifiable information about yourself. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

### 9\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. Your account information is password-protected. Additionally, your account's password is stored using a salted, variable work factor, one-way hash algorithm.

In certain areas, DesignBold uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. If DesignBold learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using DesignBold or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of those sites, products and services. We may post a notice on our applicable web sites if a security breach occurs. We may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. 

### 10\. CHANGING YOUR PREFERENCES AND PERSONAL INFORMATION

You can edit your account information with DesignBold at any time. You can delete your applicable account by visiting the applicable account deletion page; we will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, however, please note that some personal information, primarily your contact information, may remain in our records to the extent necessary to protect our legal interests or document compliance with regulatory requirements. 

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete such information by making the change on our user home page, or by emailing our Customer Support at [hello@designbold.com.](mailto:hello@designbold.com)

### 11\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

DesignBold may revise, modify or update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your particular DesignBold account or by placing a prominent notice on our site prior to the change becoming effective.

Please contact us at [hello@designbold.com.](mailto:hello@designbold.com) with any questions regarding this Policy.
